Guide to the Gerard Salton papers
Salton, Gerard papers
- Series IV. Professional Papers Writings Books
  - Croft W.B., Parenty T.J.- A Comparison of Network Structure & a Database System Used for Document Retrieval (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Croft W.B., Lefkowitz L.S.- POISE- An Intelligent Assistant for Profession Based Systems (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Croft W.B., Lewis D.D.- Meaning Representation & Natural Language Processing for Document Retrieval (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Croft W.B. et al- Retrieving Documents by Plausible Inference (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Croft W.B., Turtle H.- A Retrieval Model for Incorporating Hypertext Links (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Croft W.B., Thompson R.H.- The Use of Adaptive Mechanisms for Selection of Search Strategies (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Croft W.B., Lewis D.D.- An Approach to Natural Language Processing for Document Retrieval (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Croft W.B., Lefkowitz L.S.- Task Support In an Office System (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Croft W.B.- Boolean Queries & Term Dependencies In Probabilistic Retrieval Models (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Croft W.B., Jing Y.- An Association Thesaurus for Information Retrieval (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Croft W.B.- Towards a "Unified" Theory of Information Access (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Croft W.B.-Clustering Large Files of Documents (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Croft W.B.-Effectiveness & Implementation of a Model of Cluster Searching (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Croft W.B., Rochfort J.-Evaluation of Text Indexing & Retrieval In the Office Environment (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Croft W.B.- A Model of Cluster Searching based on Classification (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Croft W.B.- Using Boolean Queries with a Clustered File Organization (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Croft W.B., Savino P.- Ranking Strategies Using Text Signatures (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Croft W.B.- Experiments with Representation In a Document Retrieval System (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Croft W.B., Harper D.J.- Using Probabilistic Models of Document Retrieval without Relevance Information (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Croft W.B., Wolf R., Thompson R.- A Network Organization used for Document Retrieval (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Croft W.B., Thompson R.H.- An Expert Assistant for Document Retrieval (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Croft W.B., Thompson R.H.-IR, A New Approach to the Design of Document Retrieval Systems (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Croft W.B., Turtle H.- A Retrieval Model for Incorporating Hypertext Links (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Croft W.B. et al- Retrieving Documents by Plausible Inference (Box 36, Folder 40-a)
  - Croft W.B.- Document Representation In Probabilistic Models of Information Retrieval (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Croft W.B.- A Comparison of the Cosine Correlation & the Modified Probabilistic Model (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Crouch D.B., Salton G.- The Visual Display of Information Retrieval Environment (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Crouch D.B.- A File Organization & Maintenance Procedure for Dynamic Document Collections (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Crouch C.- Local Thesaurus (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - Crouch C.J., Nance R.E.- An Approach to the Functional Description of an Information Retrieval System (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - Crouch C.J.- An Analysis of Approximate versus Exact Discrimination Values (Box 36, Folder 47)
  - Crouch C.J.- A Cluster Based Approach to Thesaurus Construction (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - Cryptography (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - Caudra C.A., Katter R.V.- Experimental Studies of Relevance Judgments: Final Report-I (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - Caudra C.A., Katter R.V.- Experimental Studies of Relevance Judgments: Final Report-II (Box 36, Folder 51)
  - Caudra C.A.-On the Utility of the Relevance Concept (Box 36, Folder 52)
  - Caudra C.A., Katter R.V.- Opening the Black Box of Relevance (Box 36, Folder 53)
  - Curtice R., Jones P.E.- Distributional Constraints & the Automatic Selection of an Indexing Vocabulary (Box 36, Folder 54)
  - Curtice R., Jones P.E.-An Operational Interactive Retrieval System (Box 36, Folder 55)
  - Curvalle B., Bouroche J.M.- La Recherche Documentaire par Voisinage (Box 36, Folder 56)
  - Dabrowski M., Laus K.- Information Retrieval for Hierarchical Set of Descriptors (Box 36, Folder 57)
  - Cutting D.R. et al- Scatter/ Gather: A Cluster- Based Approach to Browsing Large Document Collections (Box 36, Folder 58)
  - Dahlberg I.A.- On the Theory of the Concept (Box 36, Folder 59)
  - Dahlberg I.A.- Grundlagen Universaler Wissensordnung (Box 36, Folder 60)
  - Dahlberg I.A.- Entwurf Fur Ein Deskriptorsystem der Informationswissenschaften als Basis Eins Bareichthesaurus (Box 36, Folder 61)
  - Dale A.G., Dale N., Pendergraft P.D.- A Programming System for Automatic Classification with Applications In Linguistic & Information Retrieval Research (Box 36, Folder 62)
  - Dale A.G.- Retrieval System Experimentation & Evaluation at LRC (Box 36, Folder 63)
  - Dale A.G., Dale N.- Clumping Techniques & Associative Retrieval (Box 36, Folder 64)
  - Damashek M.- N- Grams: Language Independent Categorization of Text (Box 36, Folder 65)
  - Damerau F.J.- On "Fuzzy" Adjectives (Box 36, Folder 66)
  - Damerau F.J., Mandelbrot B.B.- Tests of the Degree of Word Clustering In Samples of Written English (Box 36, Folder 67)
  - Damerau F.J.- The Use of Function Word Frequencies as Indicators of Style (Box 36, Folder 68)
  - Damerau F.J.- The Transformational Question Answering System (Box 36, Folder 69)
  - Damerau F.J.- Evaluating Computer Generated Domain Oriented Vocabularies (Box 36, Folder 70)
  - Dammers H.F.- Phased Transition From Non Mechanized Information Storage & Retrieval to Online Computer Operation (Box 36, Folder 71)
  - Darlington J.L.- Machine Methods for Proving Logical Arguments Expressed In English (Box 36, Folder 72)
  - Dasgupta P.- Boolean Interpretation of Conjunctions for Document Retrieval (Box 36, Folder 73)
  - Dasgupta P.- On Generalizing the Two Poisson Model (Box 36, Folder 74)
  - Dasgupta P.- Intelligent Information Retrieval Using Rough Set Approximations (Box 36, Folder 75)
  - Databases (Box 36, Folder 76)
  - Database Management for Text (Box 36, Folder 77)
  - Database Systems (Box 36, Folder 78)
  - Data Dictionaries (Box 36, Folder 79)
  - Dattola R.T.- Automatic Classification In Document Retrieval Systems-I, Chapters 1-4 (Box 36, Folder 80)
  - Dattola R.T.- Automatic Classification In Document Retrieval Systems-II, Chapters 5-6 (Box 36, Folder 81)
  - Dattola R.T.- FIRST- Flexible Information Retrieval System for Text (Box 36, Folder 82)
  - Dattola R.T., Murray R.M.- An Experiment In Automatic Thesaurus Construction (Box 36, Folder 83)
  - Dattola R.T.- A Fast Algorithm for Automatic Classification (Box 36, Folder 84)
  - Dattola R.T., Melzer H., Weiss S.- Proposal for an Online Retrieval System (Box 36, Folder 85)
  - Dattola R.T., Miller D.- Methods for Estimating the Number of Relevant Documents In a Collection (Box 36, Folder 86)
  - Dattola R.T.- Some Ideas for Estimating the Number of Relevant Documents (Box 36, Folder 87)
  - Davenport W.C.- CAS Computer Based Information Services (Box 36, Folder 88)
  - Davis R.- Cost Analysis of Possible Biomedical Communication Services (Box 36, Folder 89)
  - Davis R.- Individualized Education & the Individualized Communications Module of the Lister Hill Center (Box 36, Folder 90)
  - Davis R.- Planning for an Online Bibliographic Access Service (Box 36, Folder 91)
  - Davis R.- Technology In Support of Medical Education (Box 36, Folder 92)
  - Davis R.- The Audiovisual Problem (Box 36, Folder 93)
  - Davis R.M.- The National Biomedical Communications Network as a Developing Structure (Box 36, Folder 94)
  - Dearden J.- Myth of Real-time Management Information (Box 36, Folder 95)
  - Donald de B.Beaver- A Statistical Study of Scientific & Technical Journals (Box 36, Folder 96)
  - Debili F., Fluhr C, Radosoa P.- About Reformulation In Full Text IRS (Box 36, Folder 97)
  - Decresy F., Hirschberg L.- La Notion de Formant (Box 36, Folder 98)
  - Deerwester S.C.- The Retrieval Expert Model of Information Retrieval (Box 36, Folder 99)
  - Deerwester S.C. et al- Indexing by Latent Semantic Analysis (Box 36, Folder 100)
  - Defense Documentation Center- D.D.C Information (Box 36, Folder 101)
  - De Gennaro R.- Automation: Changing Patterns & New Directions (Box 36, Folder 102)
  - Publications by Others- Continued (D..) (Box 37)
  - DeGennaro R.- Austerity, Technology & Resource Sharing, Research Libraries Face the Future (Box 37)
  - DeGennaro R.- Automation In the Harvard College Library (Box 37)
  - DeGennaro R.- The Development & Administration of Automated Systems In Academic Libraries (Box 37)
  - deGroiler E.-Computer Produced Shelf List (Box 37)
  - deGroiler E.-On the Theoretical Basis of Information Retrieval Systems (Box 37)
  - deHeer T.- Homosemy In Natural Language Information Retrieval (Box 37)
  - deJong G.- An Overview of the FRUMP System (Box 37)
  - Delobel C.- Normalization & Hierarchical Dependencies In the Relational Data Model (Box 37)
  - deMaine P.A.D., Raphael B.S., Whitten D.E.- A Global Memory System I, Design Overview (Box 37)
  - deMaine P.A.D., Marron B.A.- The SOLID System, A Method for Organizing & Searching Files (Box 37)
  - Demaio A., Pastro A.J.- SMART Distribution System (Box 37)
  - Dempster- Shafer Belief Theory (Box 37)
  - Dennis S.F.- Automatic Indexing Searching Study-I (Box 37)
  - Dennis S.F.- Automatic Indexing Searching Study -II (Box 37)
  - Dennis S.F.- The Construction of a Thesaurus Automatically from a Sample of Text (Box 37)
  - Dempster- Shafer Belief Theory- Slides (Box 37)
  - Dennis S.F.- The Design & Testing of a Fully Automatic Indexing Searching System for Documents Consisting of Expository Text (Box 37)
  - Deogun J.S., Raghavan V.V., Tsou T.K.W.- Organization of Clustered Files for Consecutive Retrieval (Box 37)
  - Derose S.J.- Grammatical Category Disambiguation by Statistical Optimization (Box 37)
  - Desktop Publishing (Box 37)
  - deSolla Price D.J.- Is Technology Historically Independent of Science? (Box 37)
  - Detant M., Leroy A.- Elaboration D'un Programme D'Analyse de la Signification (Box 37)
  - Deussen P.- Documentation (Box 37)
  - deVarennes R.- Online Serials System at Laval University Library (Box 37)
  - Dewar H., Bratley P., Thorne J.P.- A Program for the Syntactic Analysis of English Sentences (Box 37)
  - Dewitt D.J. et al- Implementation Techniques for Main Memory Database Systems (Box 37)
  - DIAGRAM- A Grammar for Dialogues (Box 37)
  - Diamond D.S., Selwyn L.L.- Considerations for Computer Utility Pricing Policies (Box 37)
  - DIANA Project- Automatic Document Encoding & Retrieval System (Box 37)
  - Dickson D.H.- Wortstammretrieval: Ein Studie zu Gegenwartigen Lage In Praxis Und Forschung (Box 37)
  - Dictionaries (Box 37)
  - Dictionary Lookup of Words (Box 37)
  - Diday E.- Problems of Clustering & Recent Advances (Box 37)
  - Diday E.- The Dynamic Clusters Method & Sequentialization In Non-Hierarchical Clustering (Box 37)
  - DIENST: Implementation Reference Manual (Box 37)
  - Digital Libraries (Box 37)
  - Diller T., Olney J.- SOLAR ( A Semantically Oriented Lexical Archive)- Current Status & Plans (Box 37)
  - Dillon M, Federhart P.- Statistical Recognition of Content Terms In General Text (Box 37)
  - Dillon M, Federhart P.- The Use of Discriminant Analysis to Select Content-Bearing Words (Box 37)
  - Dillon M.- Fully Automatic Book Indexing (Box 37)
  - Dillon M., Gray A.S.- FASIT: A Fully Automatic Syntactically Based Indexing System (Box 37)
  - Diday E., Hanani U.- Multi-criteria Dynamic Clustering (Box 37)
  - Dillon M., Caplan P.- A Technique for Evaluating Automatic Term Clustering (Box 37)
  - Dillon M.- Serving the Information Needs of Scientific Research (Box 37)
  - Dillon M., Desper J.- The Use of Automatic Relevance Feedback In Boolean Retrieval Systems (Box 37)
  - Dimsdale J.J.- File Structure for an Online Catalog of One Million Titles (Box 37)
  - Winchester Disks (Box 37)
  - Distributed Information Systems (Box 37)
  - DOBIS- Dortmund Library System, DOBIS Application Guide (Box 37)
  - Dobrowolski Z.- Analyse Des Systemes de Classification (Box 37)
  - Document Architecture (Box 37)
  - Document Preparation Systems (Box 37)
  - Document Space Modification (Box 37)
  - Dodd G.G.- Elements of Data Management Systems (Box 37)
  - Dolby J.L.- On the Notions of Ambiguity & Information In Information Sets (Box 37)
  - Dolby J.L., Earl L.L., Resnikoff H.L.- The Application of English Word Morphology to Automatic Indexing & Extracting (Box 37)
  - Dolobel C., Casey R.G.- Decomposition of a Database & the Theory of Boolean Switching Functions (Box 37)
  - Donkin R.G.- "Mini" Information System (Box 37)
  - Dorr J.R.- IBM Document Processing System (Box 37)
  - Doszkocs T.E., Rapp A.R.- Searching Medline In English (Box 37)
  - Doszkocs T.E.- Natural Language Processing (Box 37)
  - Doszkocs T.E.- AID- Associative Interactive Dictionary for Online Bibliographic Searching (Box 37)
  - Doszkocs T.E., Rapp B.A., Schoolman H.M.-Automated Information Retrieval In Science & Technology (Box 37)
  - Doyle L.B.- Indexing & Abstracting by Association (Box 37)
  - Doyle L.B.- Semantic Road Maps for Literature Searches (Box 37)
  - Doyle L.B.- Programmed Interpretation of Text (Box 37)
  - Doyle L.B.- Recent Developments In the Plan for Statistical Classification of Large Numbers In Documents (Box 37)
  - Doyle L.B.- The Story of Language Processing & Retrieval at SDC (Box 37)
  - Doyle L.B.- Sixty Ideas In Sixty Months (Box 37)
  - Doyle L.B.- Perpetual User Studies (Box 37)
  - Doyle L.B.- Expanding the Editing Function In Language Data Processing (Box 37)
  - Doyle L.B.- Is Relevance an Adequate Criterion In Retrieval System Evaluation? (Box 37)
  - Doyle L.B.- Statistical Analysis of Text In the Distant Future (Box 37)
  - Doyle L.B.- Associations Derived from Text (Box 37)
  - Doyle L.B.- Statistical Semantics (Box 37)
  - Doyle L.B.- Technical Advances In Automatic Classification (Box 37)
  - Doyle L.B.- Is Automatic Classification A Reasonable Application of Statistical Analysis of Text? (Box 37)
  - Doyle L.B.- Some Compromises between Word Grouping & Document Grouping (Box 37)
  - Doyle L.B.- The Micro statistics of Text (Box 37)
  - Doyle L.B.- How to Plot a Breakthrough (Box 37)
  - Doyle L.B.- Breaking the Cost Barrier In Automatic Classification (Box 37)
  - Drew D.L. et al- An Online Technical Library Reference Retrieval System (Box 37)
  - Drew D.L.- Two Reference Retrieval Dialogues (Box 37)
  - Dreyfus H.L.- What Computers Still Can't Do- A Critique of Artificial Reason (Box 37)
  - Dreyfus H.L.- Alchemy & Artificial Intelligence (Box 37)
  - Driver E.H.C. et al- The Birmingham Libraries' Cooperative Mechanization Project (Box 37)
  - Drummond M.E. Jr.- A Perspective on System Performance Evaluation (Box 37)
  - Dubes R., Jain A.K.- Clustering Techniques- The User's Dilemma (Box 37)
  - Dude R.O., Hart P.E.- Pattern Classification & Science Analysis (Box 37)
  - Duggan M.- Library Network Analysis & Planning (Box 37)
  - Dujmovic J.J.- Evaluation, Comparison & Optimization of Hybrid Computers Using the Theory of Complex Criteria (Box 37)
  - Dunham G.S., Graitson M.- Auto Indexing In Pathology (Box 37)
  - Durand C.X.- Forward Multidimensional Search with Application to Information Retrieval Systems (Box 37)
  - Dym E.D.- Relevance Predictability I&II (Box 37)
  - Eastman C.M.- Optimal Bucket Size for Mutli-attribute Retrieval In Partitioned Files (Box 37)
  - Eastman C.M.- Handling Incrementally Specified Boolean Queries (Box 37)
  - Eastman W.- A Compressed Cross Index for Information Retrieval (Box 37)
  - Eastman W.L.- Linear Programming with Pattern Constrains (Box 37)
  - Eastman W.L.- A Row- Compressed Information Retrieval File (Box 37)
  - Eastwood Commons Residents Association (Box 37)
  - Ebright J.R.-Technical Information Program (TIP) (Box 37)
  - Ecole D'Humanite (Box 37)
  - Edelberg M., Wong K.C.- Interval Hierarchies & their Application to Predicate Files (Box 37)
  - Editing- Mark up System (Box 37)
  - Edmundson H.P.- Mathematical Models of Text (Box 37)
  - Edmundson H.P.- New Methods In Automatic Extracting (Box 37)
  - Education (Box 37)
  - Educational Facilities Labs, Inc.- The Impact of Technology on the Library Building (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Egan D.E., Lesk M.E., et al - CORE Project (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Egghe L. - Relative Concentration (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Fedorowicz J. - Bibliometrics (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Goldfarb L. - Associative Memories (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Shasha D., Wang T. - Best Match Retrieval (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Egghe L. - IR Based on Relative Concentration (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Eisman S.H. - A Polish-Type Notation for Chemical Structures (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Electronic Journal (ViewData) (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Electronic Mail (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Electronic Fund Transfer (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Email Discrimination (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Enigma Solution (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Equipment (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Elliot R., Cashman L. - A Relevance-Feedback Experiment (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - ERIC Clearinghouse (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Ernst M. L., Giuliano V.E., Jones P.E. - Centralization of Document Searching Facilities (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - EUREKA Retrieval System - T.G. Burket, P.A. Emrath (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Europe Science (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Evans D. (CMU) - CLARIT Project (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Evans L. - Search Strategy in SDI Profiles (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Expert Systems - T.R. Addis (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Evans D.A., Lefferts R.G. - CLARIT-TREC-2 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Extended Boolean Retrieval (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Fagan J. - Thesis (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Fagan J.L. - Nonsyntactic Approach to Phrase Indexing (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Fagan J.L. - Syntactic Info in Content Analysis (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Fagan J. - Query Expansion Based on MST (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Fagan J.L. - Auto Phrase Indexing (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Fagan J., Scott M.A. - Phrase Display (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Fairthorne R.A. - The Information Revolution - A Britisher's Perspective (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Fairthorne R.A. - Basic Parameters of Retrieval Tests (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Fairthorne R.A. - Content Analysis Specification and Control (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Fairthorne R.A. - Morphology of Information Flow (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Fairthorne R.A. - Progress in Documentation: Emperical Hyperbolic Distributions for Bibliometric Description and Prediction (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Fairthorne R.A. - Documentary Classification as a Self-Organizing System 1960 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Fairthorne R.A. - Matching of Operational Language in Documentary Systems (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Fairthorne R.A. - An Outsider Inside Information: USA 1961-1962 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Fairthorne R.A. - "Use" and "Mention" in the Information Sciences (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Fallout and Generality (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Faloutsos C. - Access Methods for Text (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Faloutsos C. - Signature Files (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - Faltings B. - Qualitative Kinematics in Mechanisms (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - Fangmeyer H., Lustig G. - The EURATOM Automatic Indexing Process (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Fangmeyer H., Lustig G. - Handling of Nuclear Information - CETIS Auto. Indexing System Exp. (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - Farradane J. - The Challenge of Information Retrieval (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - Farradane J. - Relational Indexing (Box 38, Folder 47)
  - Fast Computations (Box 38, Folder 48)
  - Faulk R.D. - An Inductive Approach to Language Translation Comm. ACM Vol. 7, No.11, November 1964 (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - Fay R.J. - Full-Text Information Retrieval (Box 38, Folder 50)
  - Fay R.J. - Patent Office Search (Box 38, Folder 51)
  - Fedorov E.B. - An Algorithm for Constructing Paradigmatic Relations in Descriptor IRSs (an experiment) (Box 38, Folder 52)
  - Strips (Box 38, Folder 53)
  - Fels E.M. - Evaluation of the Performance of an Information-Retrieval Sys. by Modified Mooers Plan. (Box 38, Folder 54)
  - Ferris R.J. - An Analysis of the Multiple Instantaneous Response File. RADC-TDR-64-457 Dec. 1964 (Box 38, Folder 55)
  - International Federation for Documentation - FID Yearbook 1962 (Box 38, Folder 56)
  - Fidel R. - Expert Systems for Selecting Search Keys (Box 38, Folder 57)
  - Fiedler N., Schulze U. - Thesaurus Through Clustering (Box 38, Folder 58)
  - Field B.J. - Auto Assignment of Controlled-Language Index (Box 38, Folder 59)
  - A Technical Index of Interactive Information Systems (Box 38, Folder 60)
  - Fikes R.E., Hart P.E., Nilsson N.J. - Learning and Executing Generalized Robot Plans (Box 38, Folder 61)
  - File Organization and Access (Box 38, Folder 62)
  - Information Filtering (Box 38, Folder 63)
  - Findler N.V. - Similarity Measure Between Two Strings (Box 38, Folder 64)
  - Findley L.D., Bolze C.C., Carpenter R.A. - A Card Controlled Routine for Searching Chemical Compound Data with an IBM 704 (Box 38, Folder 65)
  - Finger S., Rinderle J.R. - Transforming Behavioral and Physical Representations of Mechanical Designs (Box 38, Folder 66)
  - Firschein O., Summit R.K. - 2nd USA-Japan Computer Conference (Box 38, Folder 67)
  - Firth F.E. - An Experiment in Literature Searching with the IBM 305 RAMAC (Box 38, Folder 68)
  - Fischer J. - Abstracting (Box 38, Folder 69)
  - Fleisher A. - Boolean Relevance Feedback (Box 38, Folder 70)
  - Floyd R.W. - The Syntax of Programming Languages: A Survey (Box 38, Folder 71)
  - Fortuna R.M. - Quality Function Deployment (Box 38, Folder 72)
  - Fossum E.G., et al. - Multi-List System: Final Notes on a Study into Automatic Attribute Group Assignment - Tech. Memo (Box 38, Folder 73)
  - Fox E.A. - Application of "Meaning <= Text" Model (Box 38, Folder 74)
  - Fox E.A. - Passage Retrieval (Box 38, Folder 75)
  - Fox E.A. - SMART for Minicomputers (Box 38, Folder 76)
  - Fox E.A. - Contours P-Norm (Box 38, Folder 77)
  - Fox E.A., France R.K. - Expert System for Document Analysis - CODER (Box 38, Folder 78)
  - Fox E.A. - Extended Vector Retrieval (Box 38, Folder 79)
  - Fox E.A. - Composite Document Retrieval (Box 38, Folder 80)
  - Fox E.A., Sharon S. - Two Methods of Soft Boolean Proc. (Box 38, Folder 81)
  - Fox E. - INGRES on VAX (Box 38, Folder 82)
  - Fox E.A. - Lexical Relations (Box 38, Folder 83)
  - Fox E.A., Lee W.C. - Interpreting Boolean Queries (Box 38, Folder 84)
  - Fox E.A. - Collections (CACM, ISI) (Box 38, Folder 85)
  - Fox E.A., others - Minimal Perfect Hashing (Box 38, Folder 86)
  - Fox E.A. - IR and Networked Multimedia Info Access (Box 38, Folder 87)
  - Fox E.A., Nutter J.T. - Building a Large Thesaurus (Box 38, Folder 88)
  - Fox E.A. - Interactive Digital Multimedia (Box 38, Folder 89)
  - Fox E.A. - CD-ROM Disks (Box 38, Folder 90)
  - Fox E.A. - Relational Thesaurus (Box 38, Folder 91)
  - Fox E.A. - Linguistics and Info Science (Box 38, Folder 92)
  - Fox E.A. - Discourse Analysis (Box 38, Folder 93)
  - Fragments (Box 38, Folder 94)
  - France (Sabbatical) (Box 38, Folder 95)
  - Fraenkel A.S. - Document Indexing - A Hard Problem (Box 38, Folder 96)
  - Fraenkel A.S., Mor M., Perl Y. - Is Text Compression Practical? (Box 38, Folder 97)
  - Fraenkel A.S. - A Retrieval System for the Responsa (Box 38, Folder 98)
  - Frakes W.B. - Term Conflation (Box 38, Folder 99)
  - Frames - A.I. (Box 38, Folder 100)
  - Frants V.I., Voisnunsky V.G. - Russian Texts (Box 38, Folder 101)
  - Frants V.I., Shapiro J. - Control and Feedback in a Doc. Info. (Box 38, Folder 102)
  - Frants V., Shapiro J. - Auto Construction of Boolean (Box 38, Folder 103)
  - Freeman R.R., Atherton P. - Audacious - An Experiment with an Online, Interactive... (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Frei H.P. - Semantic Links in Hypertext Info Retrieval (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Frei H.P., Schäuble P. - Determining Effectiveness (Box 39, Folder 3)